

CONTACTS

- (+84)703540064
- daoxuannhatvy@gmail.com
- in <u>Dao Xuan Nhat Vy</u>
- District 7, Ho Chi Minh City

SOFT SKILLS

- Research & Analysis
- Critical Thinking
- Problem solving
- Project Management
- Interpersonal Skills
- Networking

Dao Xuan Nhat Vy

RMIT Economics & Finance Sophomore

ABOUT ME

Diligent, Sociable, Devoted, Tech Savvy

is how I describe myself. As a Kinesthetic Learner, I believe the best way to learn new knowledge is to catch every opportunity and get hands-on experience from it, therefore I keep myself challenged by a wide range of activities.

My 1st year at RMIT was fully Financial Technology, as it gave me chances to accelerate myself not only in Finance but also in interpersonal and intrapersonal skills.

I'm now looking forward to opportunities that can bring even more acceleration toward my skill and personal growth.

EDUCATION

- Nguyen Thi Minh Khai Highschool HCMC
- RMIT University Vietnam
 Economics & Finance | 2020 2023 (expected)

EXPERIENCES

Chief Financial Officer | RMIT Neo Culture Club April 2022 - Now

Advising Executive Board in terms of club activities

Managing organization Finance & Sponsorship

Conducting Financial Reports for School Paperwork and other parties

→ Ambassador Manager & Program Member | RMIT Fintech Blockchain Forum

November 2021

Attract more than 1000 registration. Successfully allocated and managed 15 members to achieve awareness & Registration for through multiple media channels.

Executive Business Assistant | RMIT FinTech Club March 2021 - October 2021

Successfully assist Head of Department in managing members & Internal Trainings; direct bridge between Executive Board and members; Recruited an increase of 20% quality members

Project Leader | RMIT FinTech Club

June 2021 - August 2021

Administered 4 teams (External Relationship, Programs, Marketing, Logistic) to carry out a Panel Discussion about Central Bank Digital Currency attracting more than 80 attendants, with participants of Industry-leading companies.

Project Officer | RMIT Fintech Blockchain Competition January 2021 - March 2021

National Scale Competition. Directly contribute to the overall event management. Maintain the communication between participate team and the organizer.

HARD SKILLS

Famililar with these systems:

Microsoft Office

Excel | PowerPoint | Word Outlook | Outlook Calendar | Sharepoint and other extensions

Google Workspace

Gmail | Google Drive | Google Slide | Google Docs | Google Sheets | Google Calendar | Google Meet and other extention.

• Editing Tools (Basic Level)

Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Premium Pro Canva | Capcut | Figma

Specialized Data & Process
 Visualization Tools

Power BI | Microsoft Visio

LANGUAGES

- English (IELTS 7.0 April 2021)
- Chinese (HSK 1 May 2022)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Runner up - CI Mock Interview 2022

April 2022 - Company Insider YBOX

Runner up - BUV Hackathon Challenge 2022
 January 2022 - BUV Social Innovators

 Winner - RMIT FinTech Internal Investment Competition

January 2022 - RMIT FinTech Club

Top 20 - RMIT Future Founder Competition 2021
September 2021 - RMIT university

Top 30 - Marketing Catcher 2022

April 2022 - MarC HCMC

PERSONAL INTEREST

Go game (Cờ Vây)| Piano | Frisbee | Gym workout | Reading | other new experiences (motorbike traveling, trekking, etc.)

Courses: LinkedIn Learning | Aiming for Microsoft Certificate (Exam PL-300: Microsoft Power BI Data Analyst)& Google Certificates | EdX | Coursera | Programs from RMIT

Human Psychology

FUTURE GOALS

- Internship in industry/company related to Major Interest
- CFA Level 1
- Chinese HSK 5 within 2022

It's not rocket science. Even if it truly is rocket science, there are still rocket scientists. Then why can't 1?

HOW I MOTIVATE MYSELF WHENEVER I HAVE DIFFICULTIES